Transcript: spscriptorium Sync: John Smith - forom.com
双语合成 Lv&daisy
Episode 11x14 "The List"
I'm going out to South Park gonna have myself a time
Friendly faces everywhere humble folks without temptation
I'm goin out to south park gonna leave my woes behind
Ample parking day or night people spouting howdy neighbor
I'm heading out to south park to see if i cant unwind
I like girls with big fat titties really big fat titties
So come on out to south park and meet some friends of mine
伙计们！伙计们！我的天啊！ 你们不会相信的！
Fellas! Fellas! Oh my god! You're not gonna believe this!
冷静一点
Dude, Butters, calm down.
Okay. Okay.
我跟Pete Wetchney说话时他告诉我 Danny Chadwick说
I was talking to Pete Wetchney and he said that Danny Chadwick
他的姐姐告诉他 咱们班里的女生写了一个名单
said that his sister told him that the girls in our class have a list
把男生从最帅到最丑排了号
that rates every boy's looks from cutest to ugliest.
那她们认为谁最帅？ - 我不知道
So who do they say is the cutest? - I dunno.
谁最丑？ - 我不知道！
Who do they say is the ugliest? - I don't know. It's like a girl thing.
她们不让别人看
They won't let anybody see the list but them.
她们算老几！没人可以评价咱们的长相
They can't do that. Who are they to judge us on how we look?
对 她们只是按长相排名 还是把个性也考虑了进去
Yeah. You think they rate us just for looks or they take personality into account?
如果只是长相 那我觉得我还可以
If it's just looks then I think I'm safe.
各位 谁在乎女生们的蠢蛋排名？ 女生总是做各种无聊的统计
You guys, who cares if the girls make some stupid list? Girls make dumb lists all the time.
对 kyle说的没错 管它呢 我们有更重要的事要考虑
Yeah, Kyle's right. Screw it, we have better things to worry about.
你那么说 是因为你知道 自己会排在老末儿！
You're just saying that because you know you're gonna be very last on the list!
Oh 得了吧 我不这么认为！ 小妞们觉得我比你帅多了
Oh please, I don't think so, Craig! Chicks think I'm way hotter than you!
你不知道她们会把死胖子排在老末？
You don't think they put the fat tub of tard at the bottom?
不！因为我不胖！ 我很健美！
No, because people know I'm not fat! I'm buff.
她们很可能把你排在老末儿 因为你那一口烂牙！
They probably put you at the bottom of the list because you have fucked up teeth!
或者Kenny 因为他很穷 - 他们不可能把我排在最后，不是吗？
Or Kenny's because he's poor. - They didn't put me at the bottom, did they?
Kenny 你承认吧：女生们可不想结婚之后 每天晚上吃速冻食品
Kenny, face it: Girls don't wanna eat Pop Tarts for dinner every night when they get married.
我不会是是班里最丑的男生吧，啊？
You don't think they said I'm the ugliest boy in the class, do ya?
要是的话，我爸会关我禁闭的
Well if they did, my parents will ground me.
各位，你们真的在乎 一帮女生给你们的脸打的分？
You guys, do you really care what a bunch of girls have to say about how you rank in looks?!
好吧Bebe 让我们看看排名 - 什么？
All right, Bebe, let's see the list. - What?
你知道我什么意思 臭婊子！
You know what I'm talking about, bitch!
就是你们给男生的排名！
The list where you rate the looks of each boy in the class!
那是女生们的秘密排名！ 男生不准看！
That's not for boys to look at! It's a secret girl list and you can't see it!
Craig排老末，对吗？
Craig is on the bottom, right?
或者Kenny 因为你要是和她结婚 就得每餐吃微波炉食品
Or is it Kenny because you'd be eating Pop Tarts for dinner if you married him.
我不告诉你！反正， 名单不在我这，Nelly拿着呢！
I'm not telling! And anyway, I'm not the list keeper, Nelly is!
并且Nelly永远不会让你们看的 所以 滚吧！
And Nelly will never let you look at it, so there!
操你妈 Bebe！操你全家！
Fuck you Bebe! Fuck you bitch!
完了，我看咱们永远得不到名单了
Well, I guess we're never gonna get that list from the girls.
不会的 因为我们是男人 我们比娘门儿聪明
Screw that, dude! We're guys. We can outthink them.
注意，这是我们的情报
All right, here's what we know.
傻逼Nelly负责保管名单，对吧
That chick Nelly is the one who's in charge of holding the list, right.
显然 她把名单放在一个蓝色的笔记本里 我们需要一个计划来把它弄过来
She apparently keeps it in a purple Pee Chee folder and we need a plan to get it from her.
这个计划叫： “很可能不会失败的行动”
This is what I call: "Operation: Cannot Possibly Fail"
牛B!
Neato!
明天下午一点，Nelly会去公共图书馆
At 1 p.m. tomorrow, Nelly will have to walk from Home Ec to Social Studies.
那是我们行动的好机会
That's our best time to strike.
当她穿过3号走廊时
As she makes her way through Hallway 3,
Craig负责制造点状况使她分心
Craig will be ready with a distraction device here.
当她停下来看Craig时
When she stops and turns to Craig in the hallway,
Butters 就跑过去踢她的 蛋蛋
Butters will run up and kick her in the balls.
Okay!
Butters踢了她的蛋，她就会疼得丢掉笔记本
Once Butters kicks her in the balls, she'll fall to the floor, dropping the Pee Chee,
然后Kenny　就冲过去抢本子 都明白了么？
and Kenny will swoop in from Corridor 3-Delta and grab the Pee Chee. Are we good?
你有病啊？
What you do that for?!
嘿，你找死啊，白痴？！
Hey, what's your problem, asshole?!
撤退！撤退！
Bail, bail!
虽然任务失败了 但是我们获取了宝贵的经验
Okay, our mission failed, but we've learned a lot.
最主要的是，女生没有蛋蛋 - 肯定没有
Primarily that girls do not have balls. - They sure don't.
无所谓了，因为我们有B计划
Never mind, because we are going to Plan B,
行动代号 “也许不会再一次失败的行动”
one that I call "Operation: Cannot Possibly Fail A Second Time."
当Nelly离开自助餐厅时
When Nelly leaves the cafeteria for recess,
Kenny就跳到她面前 吐一地
Kenny will jump in front of her and spit on the ground.
你觉得女生的蛋蛋是不是在胃里面？
You think maybe girls keep their balls on the inside of their tummies?
现在不是讨论这个的时候！集中注意力！
Butters, we're done talking about girls balls right now! Pay attention!
我们成功了！我们成功了！ - 我们得到了名单！
We got it! We got it! - We got the list from the girls!
把它还给我 你们这群混蛋
Give that back you dirty buttholes!
Kenny快把它贴墙上! Jason, 注意警戒!
Tape it to the wall, Kenny! Jason, watch the door!
真的是 “从最帅到最丑名单” Clyde 排第一.
It's listed in order from cutest to ugliest. Clyde's number one.
我? 我最帅?
Me? I'm the cutest?
然后是Token，再后是我。 - 我排第二？WOW.
And then Token and then me. - I'm number two? Wow.
让我看看！让我看看！
Come on, let me see!
啊 伙计们 我是第11! Whoopie! 第11!
Oh boy! I'm number 11! Whoopie! Number 11!
哈！你看！我比你帅，肥佬！ - 什嘛？！那是不可能的！
Ah! Look at that! I'm hotter than you, fatso! - What?! That's bullcrap!
各位 这有什么意义？ 你们现在满足了？
Oh, so big deal, guys! Do you feel better now?
Clyde是班里最帅的 然后是Token和Stan
Clyde's the best looking kid in the class. And then Token and Stan.
倒数三个是Fancis，Cartman和...
And last is Francis, Cartman, and...
我?
Me?
你是老末儿，宝贝！
You're last, dude!
不会吧 - 会的！再看看！
No way. - Yes way! Check it out!
Cartman一边歇着去 你不也是倒数第二 - 说明我比Kyle帅！
Cartman, lay off! You're next to last. - So? I'm hotter than Kyle.
我比Kyle长得帅! Yes! 我比Kyle受欢迎!
I'm better looking than Kyle! Yes! I'm hotter than Kyle!
我排老末儿? 老末儿?
I'm last? Last?
伙计,这只是个蠢名单，记得么? - 我是投票选出来最丑的男生?
Dude, it's just a stupid list, remember? - I got voted the ugliest boy in whole class?
谁在乎傻女人的想法呢,对吧 ?
Who cares what dumb girls think, right?
Mom, Dad! 我不是班里最丑的男生! Kyle Broflovski 才是!
Mom, Dad! I'm not the ugliest kid in the class! Kyle Broflovski is!
有一套啊, 小子 - 不错
Well good for you, Butters. - Way to go, champ.
Whoopie!
Well, 看来不用关他禁闭了
Well, guess we don't have to ground him.
Kyle, 怎么了? 你一点也没吃啊
Kyle, what's the matter? You barely touched your knishes.
学校的女生, 评我为最丑的男生
The girls at school. They made a list and voted me the ugliest boy.
What? 岂有此理 我的小宝贝儿很可爱!
What? That's ridiculous. My little bubbeleh is adorable!
Look, 我知道我不是最帅的, 可我也不认为我很丑啊
Look, I know I'm not the best-looking guy in town, but I didn't think I was the very ugliest.
你一点也不丑, Kyle. 你是个完美的小伙子 你长得就像你爸爸一样
You're not ugly, Kyle. You're my perfect little man. You look just like your father.
天哪 是吗
Oh God! I do?
你还有一个像你妈妈一样的鼻子
But he has his mother's nose.
Kyle,你不管怎么看都非常帅!
Kyle, you are very handsome and perfect in every way.
Ike,你要诚实一点 我很丑吗, yes or no?
Ike, you have to be honest. Am I ugly, yes or no?
你们都认为我丑 上帝啊 至少你们可以跟我直说吧!
You all think I'm ugly. Jesus Christ, the least you could have done is told me!
Kyle, 回来!
Kyle, come back here!
我比你长得帅!
I'm better-looking than you!
女生们认为我长得比你帅, Kyle!
The girls think I'm better-looking than you, Kyle!
听见了吗?
Dude, Kyle. Can you hear me?
她们认为我长得比你帅多了!
They totally think I'm hotter than you are.
Kyle!
Kyle,我更有吸引力.
Kyle, I'm more attractive.
Kyle?
Clyde,该睡觉了
Clyde, it's time to be getting to bed.
嘿 最近怎么样?
Hey, what's going on?
最近怎么样? Hey.
What's going on? Hey.
Oh 耶 嘿 有空吗? 最近怎么样?
Oh yeah, hey, whassup? What's going on?
帅.
Nice.
嘿, 最近怎么样? - 嘿 Clyde.
Hey, what's going on? - Hey Clyde.
嘿.
- Hi Clyde. Hey. - Hi Clyde.
最近怎么样?
What's going on?
嘿 丑八怪!
Hey ugly!
Hey, Kyle. 其实,别人怎么看你 根本无所谓 , 对吧?
Hey, Kyle. Look man, it doesn't matter what people think, okay?
亚伯拉罕·林肯也很丑 可是你看他的成就
You know, Abraham Lincoln was pretty ugly too, but look what he accomplished.
自信点,伙计
Chin up, cowboy.
嘿, 最近怎么样? - Oh, 还好, 没什么事-
Hey, what's going on? - Oh, not much, just hanging around-
嘿, 耳朵好漂漂呀 大饼脸!
Hey, nice nice ears. Pizza Face!
Butters, 这样可不对 他不能决定自己长什么样
Butters, that's not cool, man. He can't help how he looks.
Kyle, 我有个小小建议 也许你应该...
Kyle, I was going to suggest that maybe you should...
和学校里其他丑孩子一起玩
hang out with the other ugly kids in the school.
因为如果你和他们在一起, 你就不那么显眼了 对吧?
Because if you hang out with them, you won't stand out so much. Right?
酷.
Cool.
嘿.
Hey.
你好
Hello.
你还吃你的泡菜吗?
Are you going to eat your pickle?
谁去把足球捡回来? 就在那些丑孩子旁边
Could somebody toss the football back? It's over there next to the ugly kids.
我憎恨上学 这让我感到很愤怒
I hate coming to this school. It makes me angry.
嗯
Yeah.
有时我真想把学校给烧了 烧得一干二净!
Sometimes I just want to burn it down. Burn the whole school down to the ground!
不 你错了 大错特错!我们不丑!
No. You know what? Screw this! We aren't ugly!
我们不丑? - 一点也不!
We're not? - No!
也许我们只是需要改变一点形象 就是化化妆之类的
Maybe we all just need a little image change, you know? Like a makeover.
好像是
Hey yeah.
比如你! 可能你只需要把头发压一压
Like you! Maybe you just need to let your hair down.
再试试不戴眼镜会看起来怎么样
And let's see how you look without those glasses.
还是戴上吧
Let's just put those back on.
我知道,那首歌实在是太屌了
I know, that song is so awesome.
Wendy. 能跟你说句话么? - 当然, Stan.
Wendy. Could I talk to you? - Of course, Stan.
就一分钟 去那吧
Just for a minute. Over here.
你说他们是不是要和好了?
You think he's gonna beg her to come back to him?
真让我吃惊 我还以为 你再也不和我说话了呢
This is a nice surprise. I thought you were never speaking to me again.
唔 我想跟你谈谈你们统计的那个排名
Yeah well, I wanna talk to you about this list you girls made.
哪个排名? 我们统计了很多排名
Which one? We make lists all the time.
关于男生长相的那个
The one where you rated the boys looks in the class.
它对Kyle的打击太大了, okay? 你们怎么会都觉得他丑?
Look, it really messed Kyle up, okay? How could you vote him the ugliest?
说真的 我个人并没投他的票
Look, personally, I didn't vote him the ugliest.
我投的是 Eric Cartman 但是 一定有很多其他的女生觉得他-
My vote was for Eric Cartman. But enough of the other girls must have felt he was-
你也这么觉得吧 也许你们可以修改一下排名
So it was unanimous. Maybe you can just change the list.
修改排名?! 你知道那意味着什么吗?!
Change the list?! Do you have any idea what that would take?!
你根本不明白 排名对女生来说有多重要!
Maybe you don't understand how important list-making is to girls!
那可不是什么随随便便的东西! 我们有严格的制度!
It's just not something we do flippantly! There's protocol!
我们能不能问问其她的女生们 为什么她们都把Kyle排在老末儿?
Can't we just talk to all the girls who made the list and find out why they voted Kyle last?
好吧 我会尽力让你能参加下一个排名大会 但你不要抱太大希望
All right, I'll try and get you into our next list-making meeting. But it won't be easy.
我宣布 今天的排名大会 现在开始 Rebecca 请你发言
Today's list meeting is called to order. Rebecca, you have the floor.
如果大家都没有异议的话 我建议继续讨论第47D号排名:
If it pleases and sparkles I suggest we continue deliberations on List 47D:
"哪位女生 拥有最可爱的钱包"
Which Girl Has The Cutest Purse?
Rebecca 提议继续第47D号排名 大家都同意么?
Rebecca moves we work on List 47D. Does that sparkle with all the girls?
同意
Sunshine.
开始讨论"哪位女生 拥有最可爱的钱包"? Milly 发言
Deliberating "Which Girl Has The Cutest Purse"? Milly has the floor.
如果大家都没有异议的话
If it pleases and sparkles,
我认为Jennifer的钱包 可以说是最可爱的
I would like to submit that Jennifer's purse is by far the cutest.
绝对要比Teresa的钱包可爱
Definitely cuter than Teresa's.
我认为在座的各位都不反对 Jennifer的钱包比Teresa的可爱
I don't think anyone here disagrees that Jennifer's purse is cuter than Teresa's,
但那并不代表她的是最可爱的
but it doesn't make it the cutest.
委员会已经决定了 有条纹的钱包都不能进入前5名
The committee has already decided that nothing with stripes can be in the Top 5 cutest purses.
下一个请Wendy发言
Sunshine sparkle Wendy has the floor.
如果大家都没有异议 我建议我们重新...
If it pleases and sparkles, I would like to suggest that we...
重新讨论上星期的排名 - 她说什么? 她在开玩笑吧!
That we reopen last week's list for debate. - What'd she say? She's gotta be kidding!
她疯了?
Is she crazy?
好吧 请站到主席台前
All right, come before the Rainbow Railing.
说啊
Go ahead.
我觉得 你们表决最丑的男生时 是不是有点轻率?
I was just thinking that maybe you voted a little hastily on the cutest boy?
你觉得你应该是第一? - 我没说
You thought you should be number one? - No.
我向你保证 我们委员会 从未轻率地对待过任何一个排名!
Let me assure you that no list is made hastily by this committee!
他不是那个意思 他只是想让我们重新讨论一下
He didn't mean that. He was just saying maybe we should open it up again for discussion.
根据排名法 我不能举行一场旧排名研讨会
I cannot by Sparkle Law move to have an old list investigated.
但是 如果你能找到调查的必要性 Wendy 我们会考虑的
However, if you can find recourse for such an inquiry, Wendy, I would review it.
姐妹们 你们都同意吗?
Does that sparkle with all the girls?
同意
Sunshine.
所有人都嘲笑我!
They all laugh at me!
女生们在我背后窃笑! 甚至都不愿意看我一眼
And the girls giggle behind my back! Unable to even glance at my disfigured face.
不要放火烧学校 Kyle
Do not burn down the school, Kyle.
谁在说话? - 是我
Who said that? - I did.
你知道我是谁吗? - 林肯?
Do you know who I am? - Abraham Lincoln?
在下就是亚伯拉罕· 林肯 放火烧学校是不能解决你的问题的
I am Abraham Lincoln. Burning down the school will not solve your problems.
你觉得上天对你不公平 因为你生来丑陋
You think you've been cheated because you are ugly,
可是我将使你看到事情的另一面 快来! 有很多地方要去
but I am here to show you otherwise. Come! There is much to see.
请你看看这儿
I want you to look in here.
这位女士是 Nancy Pinkerton.
This woman is Nancy Pinkerton.
她小时候是全校公认最漂亮的女生
As a child she was consistently the most beautiful girl in her entire school.
她的青年时期充满了奉承 生活一帆风顺
Her life as a youth was filled with praises and everything being handed to her.
男生们跟她说 “你很特殊 你很有趣 你很漂亮”
Boys told her she was special. She was funny. She was interesting.
其实只是因为他们想跟她上床
But that's only because she was hot.
一直到她40岁 当她的美貌开始消褪时
It wasn't until she reached age 40, when her looks started to fade,
她才发现自己的“特殊、漂亮” 其实只是一些泡沫
that she learned she was actually about as interesting and special, as a wet carrot.
这是你的丑朋友 Yamal的家
This is the home of your new ugly friend, Yamal.
因为长得丑 他总是被冷落
Because he's ugly, he gets nothing handed to him.
所以他不懈努力来实现自己的价值
He has to work at making something of himself.
当他长大成人后 他的努力将使他受益匪浅
But that work is gonna pay off when he's an adult.
他会有坚韧不拔的品质 而漂亮孩子很少会那样
He will have character, something that kids who are hot rarely develop.
就像你同学 Clyde.
Like your classmate, Clyde.
他知道自己长得帅以后 就不再努力了
Now that he knows he's good-looking, he doesn't have to make any effort to be special.
不是啦 Rebecca只是普通的朋友 我只想和你好
No, Rebecca's just a friend. I wanna be with you now.
好啊 我当然会给你买几双新鞋
Sure, yeah, I'll buy you some shoes too.
从此 他的生活只是泡妞
Now his life will be about girls.
把时间浪费在给女生打电话上 然后给她们买鞋子
Chatting with them on the phone and buying them shoes.
他很可能早早就结婚了
He will most likely marry very young,
然后直到40岁 才发现自己其实是个傻B
and not realize until age 40 that he's a total douche.
现在你明白了 Kyle 长得漂亮的孩子 其实是很可悲的
And so you see, Kyle, it is actually the beautiful kids that are cursed.
我可不想等到长大了才开始快乐 那实在太遥远了
But I can't wait to be an adult to be happy. That's forever from now.
要有耐心 - 快把我送回家吧!
You must be patient. - Just take me home!
我不想在这待着了! 送我回家!
I don't wanna be here anymore! Take me home!
哎 好吧
Very well.
Kyle 你需要好好想想我对你说的话
Kyle, you need to think about what I've told you.
我不! 我不想任何人教我怎么思考问题!
I don't want to! I don't want anybody telling me how to feel anymore!
那你他妈的就是个垃圾!
Well then you're just a fucking asshole!
等等 Stan 我想我发现了一些东西!
Wait a minute. Wait, Stan, I think I've got something!
看这里: 在上次的最帅男生投票中
Take a look at this: during final deliberation of the list for cutest boy,
七个女生才有一个评给Clyde一颗星
seven girls gave Clyde a glitter rating of only one sparkle.
我一点也不知道你在说什么 - 数对不上
I have no idea what you're talking about. - It doesn't add up.
很可能是Rebecca 统计选票的时候
It is possible that Rebecca made a mistake
出了一点错
when she tallied the sunshine votes onto the final list.
噢 嘿 Wendy.
Oh, hey Wendy.
嘿 Rebecca 你还留着给男生长相排名的投票么?
Hey Rebecca. Do you still have the voter cards for the list that rated the boys looks?
Wendy 我们已经结束那个排名了
Wendy, we're done with that list.
我知道 可我好像发现了一点错误
I know, but I think there's been a mistake.
我询问过的女生中 有6个都没选Clyde最帅
Six of the girls I've talked to didn't vote Clyde the cutest.
从数学的角度看他根本不可能-
That means that mathematically he should have been-
停一下 不要再追究下去了!
All right, you need to stop. Digging. Around, Wendy!
你不会喜欢你调查的结果的!
You might not like what you find!
放弃吧 不要再追问了!
Just back off and stop asking questions!
你正在接近一个会使你陷入危险的秘密! 停手吧!
You're getting close to a secret that I don't think you can handle! Let it go!
她好像不太爽, 是么?
That didn't sparkle with her, did it?
一罐丙烷 六桶燃油
One canister of propane, six cans of lighter fluid,
七加仑高热煤油 和一盒火柴
seven gallons of high-octane kerosene and a box of matches.
Okay 就这些吗 小伙子? - 这些应该足够了
Okay, is that everything, little boy? - That should just about do it.
你有积分卡么?
Do you like to put this on your True-Value card today?
尊敬的主席、秘书长
Honorary Chair, Mrs. Secretary,
我相信 有位委员对一份排名动了手脚
I believe a member of our committee has tampered with one of our lists.
根据我的调查和计算 发现Clyde不可能被选为最帅的男生
I've compiled a full report and it turns out that nobody voted Clude the cutest in the class.
我相信 是Rebecca改动了名单 使他成为第一
I believe Rebecca changed the list to make him number one.
她为什么那样做呢? - 排名一出来
Why would she do that? - Right after the list was made,
Rebecca就开始和Clyde约会 这其中是不是有什么联系?
Rebecca started going out with Clyde. You can read all the discrepancies here.
我们应该重新制定那份排名
We need to remake that list.
你就是要钻牛角尖!
You just couldn't let it go!
什么意思? 我们应该召集女生们 - 恐怕不行 Wendy!
What do you mean? Call the girls in. - I'm afraid we can't do that, Wendy!
你知道吗 Wendy Clyde的爸爸是镇上精品鞋店的老板?
Did you know, Wendy, that Clyde's father own the shoe store at the mall?
很多女生都想和Clyde约会 来得到新鞋
A lot of us have always wanted to date Clyde to get free shoes,
但我们不能 因为他不够受欢迎
but we couldn't, because he wasn't popular enough.
你们故意的!
You knew!
不幸的是 Clyde被选为倒数第5!
Unfortunately, the members voted Clyde in the bottom five of the list!
所以我们暗箱操作 打造出一份新的排名 把真的 藏起来
That's why we had to manipulate the votes, forge a new list and hide the real one!
然后你们就可以光明正大的和Clyde约会 让他买鞋?!
So that you all could justify dating Clyde and get shoes?!
你们怎么能这样滥用权力!
How dare you take advantage of your position!
我要告诉Bebe 让你们俩都从委员会除名!
I'm gonna tell Bebe and have you both disbarred from the list committee!
Bebe?! 你以为这是谁想出来的计划?!
Bebe?! Who do you think authorized the buyout?!
不 不要是她
No. Not Bebe.
她开始和Clyde约会了 她爱死精品鞋了
She's dating Clyde now. Nobody loves shoes more than her.
什么情况?
What's going on?
当其他人发现你们篡改投票 她们会-
When the other girls find out you ignored their votes, they're gonna-
她们会相信你 而不信委员会的领导们?!
Do you really think they'll believe you over the heads of the committee?!
我们只要随便搞一个新的名单! "最大的骗子"!
We'll simple generate a new list! "Biggest Liars"!
然后把你排在第一!
And put you at the top!
考虑一下你自己吧 Wendy! 停手吧! 然后闭上你的小嘴!
Do yourself a favor, Wendy! Just let it go! And keep your little mouth shut!
我看不会的!
I don't think so!
Stan,跑!
Stan, run!
上帝啊 等等!
Jesus, dude!
嘿, 看见Kyle了吗?
Hey, kid, have you seen Kyle?
我们找他有急事 但那都找不到他
We've looked everywhere and we have to show him something.
他去烧学校了 - 什么?
He's burning down the school. - What?
他说他要去把学校夷为平地
He said he gonna burn the school down to the ground.
所有的鄙视和嘲笑终要结束!
All the cruel jokes and ridicule will finally be over!
现在你高兴了吧 God?! 你让我长成这样!
Are you happy now, God?! You made me look like this!
Kyle! Kyle 别! - 不要阻止我 Stan!
Kyle! Kyle, don't! - Don't try and stop me, Stan!
你根本不理解被人当作畸形怪物的感觉!
You don't know how it feels to be a deformed monstrosity!
排名是伪造的, Kyle!
The list was a forgery, Kyle!
不是女生们的真实投票 我们找到了真正的排名
It didn't sparkle with all the girls. We have the real list.
够了! 把名单给我 Wendy!
That's about far enough! Give me that list, Wendy!
Stan 究竟是怎么回事?! - 是因为鞋子 Kyle.
Stan, what is going on?! - It was about shoes, Kyle.
女生们想要鞋子 所以他们利用你
The girls wanted shoes, so they set you up.
Kyle只是个牺牲品!
Kyle was simple a casualty!
要提升Clyde 必须把 Craig 调到第12
To move Clyde meant that Craig has to be moved to number twelve,
把Jimmy下调 把Jason提升 !
which moved Jimmy down and moved Jason up!
那我究竟是第几?
So what number was I?
你把一切都弄乱了! 我们的排名应该是真实的!
You've compromised everything! Our list's integrity!
看看这些鞋子 Wendy?! 它们太不可思议了!
Did you see these shoes, Wendy?! They're incredible!
这不是多不可思议的问题 你不能-
It doesn't matter how incredible they are. You can't-
Oh My God 这鞋太炫了 - 是吧?
Oh my God, those are amazing. - Right?
上边那是蕾丝边么? - 不，那是小鞋带
Is that a lace across the top? - No, it's a little strap.
- 但这不是理由!你太过分了!
Wendy? Wendy? - But it doesn't matter. You took it too far!
要不是你玩柯南游戏 事情早就过去了!
If you hadn't gone all Nancy Drew on us, this would have just gone away!
她要杀了我们? - 太迟了 Bebe.
She's gonna kill us? - It's too late, Bebe.
我已经写了个报告交给警察局了 真相会大白的
I've already made a full report and sent a copy to the police. People will know.
得了吧  吓唬谁啊
Oh please, you're lying.
投降吧 Bebe. 我们全都知道了 排名是伪造的
Give it up, Bebe. We know all about it. The list was compromised.
Kyle Broflovski 不是班上最丑的男生
Kyle Broflovski is not the ugliest boy in the class.
Wendy!
等等，我什么都没干 - 到局子里再解释吧
Wait, I didn't do anything wrong. - You can explain all that downtown.
给
Here, Kyle.
咱们都经历了一些事 但是 现在你可以知道自己到底是第几了
We've been through a lot, but, you can finally see where you really are on the list.
你确定这样就没事了 Kyle? - 确定。 林肯是对的
Are you sure you're okay with this, Kyle? - I'm sure. Abe Lincoln was right.
我可不想知道自己很帅 然后长大之后变成一个弱智
I don't wanna find out I'm good-looking and become a total shithead when I grow up.
林肯?
Abe Lincoln?
Stan 能我很高兴能跟你和好
Stan, it's been really great hanging out with you again.
我觉得你好像变了 变得好厉害
I feel like you've changed somehow. In a really awesome way.
嗯  事情总会变的 不是么?
Yeah well, I guess a lot of things change, don't they?